

#### $\times$

leninesteban98@outlook.co m



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



twitter.com/4fourlp? t=jgeNASSGNviB9dRdULaQB O&s=09



github.com/Lenin4lp



instagram.com/four\_lp? igshid=MzNlNGNkZWQ4Mg= =

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript

HTML



React

Bootstrap

# **LANGUAGES**

#### Spanish

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

#### English

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

## **INTERESTS**

VideoGames Dev

Web Dev

# Lenin Patiño

Software Developer

I am a highly motivated software developer from Ecuador, with a specialization in web development. I hold a degree in Software Development Technology and have successfully developed several websites. I am passionate about learning and always strive to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies in the field.

#### **FORMATION**

# **Software Development**Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Thesis:

 Developed a virtual tour for Lev Vygotsky School

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Assistant cook Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Fast Food Restaurant

Achievements/Responsabilities

- Assistant cook
- Logistics
- Teamwork

Contacto: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

## **ORGANIZATIONS**

Global Tour Group (06/2023 - WorkInProgress)

Co-founder

## **CERTIFICATES**

Expert in computer, mobile, and printer repair (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Technical specialty (04/2023 - 05/2023)

International technical expert (04/2023 - 05/2023)

## PERSONAL PROYECTS

E-Commerce Website (06/2023 - WorkInProgress)

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Top graduate of the Software Development program

Sangolquí, Ecuador.

Sangolqui, Ecuador



#### $\searrow$

leninesteban98@outlook.co m



+593 995021307



Quito, Ecuador



linkedin.com/in/leninpati%C3%B1o-135453224



twitter.com/4fourlp? t=jgeNASSGNviB9dRdULaQB Q&s=09



github.com/Lenin4lp



instagram.com/four\_lp? igshid=MzNlNGNkZWQ4Mg= =

## **COMPETENCIAS**

JavaScript

HTML



React

Bootstrap

## **IDIOMAS**

Spanish

Competencia Nativa o Bilingüe

English

Competencia Profesional de Trabajo

# **INTERESES**

Desarrollo de videojuegos

Desarrollo web

# Lenin Patiño

Desarrollador de Software

Soy un desarrollador de software ecuatoriano altamente motivado, especializado en desarrollo web. Poseo un título en Tecnología en Desarrollo de Software y he creado exitosamente varias páginas web. Me apasiona aprender y siempre me esfuerzo por mantenerme actualizado con las últimas tecnologías en el campo.

# **FORMACIÓN**

# Tecnología en Desarrollo de Software Instituto Superior Tecnológico Rumiñahui

10/2021 - 03/2023

Tesis:

 Desarrollo de un tour virtual para el colegio Lev Vygotsky

## **EXPERIENCIA LABORAL**

# **Ayudante de cocina** Chrisly

04/2018 - 04/2019

Fast Food Restaurant

Achievements/Responsabilities

- Ayudante de cocina
- Logística
- Trabajo en Equipo

Contacto: Christian Gomez - +593 984567955

## **ORGANIZACIONES**

Global Tour Group (06/2023 - Presente)

Co-fundador

## **CERTIFICADOS**

Experto en reparación de computadoras, celulares e impresoras (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Especialidad Técnica (04/2023 - 05/2023)

Experto Técnico Internacional (04/2023 - 05/2023)

## PROYECTOS PERSONALES

Sitio web E-Commerce (06/2023 - Presente)

## **LOGROS**

Mejor egresado de la carrera de desarrollo de Software

Sangolquí, Ecuador.

Sangolqui, Ecuador